[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_B",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_C",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_D",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_BellaRuby",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_E",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_E",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_B",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_C",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_08",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_09",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_10",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_09",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_10",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "CoatingAeternianT4",
  "ItemRewardQty": 3,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_completion"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Galahad_A",
  "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_12",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_title",
  "Description": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_completion_new"
 }
]